[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Looks like we can't get out of here.
We still have one option.
You really trust that informant that much.
-He's here. -Hi!
Rahmboy, the area is on lockdown.
No one's getting out.
Where are you planning to hide us?
Worse than an animal cage or a sewer, bro.
Where? Why here?
The mafia is not allowed to operate there.
The Castellanis won't make a move inside that five-star hotel.
Why haven't we heard anything on comms?
What's happening to Alex?
They're safe, but they are compromised.
We don't need to go there.
We have Mikoy's asset there who can help them.
They found us. We need to move!
Come on!
I saw her. Chiara.
Looks like she's coming back to the Philippines.
And as for the question of whether we can trust him, yes.
Mikoy's asset can be trusted.
Mom! This is for you! Fresh from Italy.
Can I talk to you?
Here’s my gift.
That should come in handy
if you want to slice Mikoy’s neck.
Seriously?
Fresh from Italy.
Come on, I could even buy that at my favorite grocery store.
Sorry, Mom.
My schedule in Italy was just too tight,
so I didn't get to buy any gifts.
You know those crazies. They're like cough syrup.
They just found out I'm going abroad,
and they already expect gifts.
What were you really doing there?
It's nothing, Mom.
It was just for the tourism.
Hey, Mikoy. Come on.
Stop lying to me.
I'm your mother, and just by looking at you,
I know when you're not telling the truth.
You know, if your father were here,
he'd be ashamed of you.
Come to think of it, you're lying to your own mother.
Fine. So I won't have to lie anymore.
Just don't ask me about it, Mom.
I just had something to take care of.
Chiara?
Did you talk to Chiara?
There's another reason why you want Mikoy gone so badly.
Like what?
But you think I still love him.
You think that if we see each other again,
if we talk,
there's a chance that he could change my mind and heart.
That's not true!
But it is.
That's why Mikoy is a threat to you.
Because you know that
if there's one person in this world I'd listen to, it's him.
After all, we have a deep history together.
Wait a minute.
Did you talk to her as Mikoy
or as a member of GAGO?
A police asset?
Mom.
Don't pull the "Mom" card on me!
Answer my question!
What's going on with you?
Did you do something wrong
because of what happened to your father?
Son,
did you take the law into your own hands?
No, Mom.
Oh, son.
Just stop this.
This won't end well, believe me.
Just learn to forgive.
To understand.
It still hurts, son.
Even I'm still completely broken to this day.
You know that.
But our pain
shouldn't dictates
how we live,
on how we make our decisions.
You know, that pain won't go away.
Even your father,
he wouldn't want this.
Even me, as your mother, I don't want this to be the life you live.
And you think
you can make me obey you because I'm under your spell.
But I'm not.
So don't ever think that you're the hero of this story.
Because anytime…
So if you want to keep existing,
never, ever tell me what I can and cannot do.
And most of all,
you have no right
to dictate who I should keep alive
or who I should kill.
I believe it'll come in handy
when I want to slit the throat of someone
who gets on my nerves.
For Mario?
Are you going to avenge your father?
Dad.
But it shouldn't be
that the pain we're feeling
-Dad! -dictates how we live our lives.
How we make our decisions.
Dad. Dad!
Mom, I'm really sorry. Dad, I'm really sorry.
If this all happened because of me.
But I have to do what I believe is right.
What is it again?!
You're going to have Chiara killed?
You heard what the Concordat said.
They're getting nervous, and they're running out of patience.
Chiara wasn't even supposed to come home to the Philippines
to meet Mikoy.
Chiara has become unpredictable.
We need to act now to protect
our position!
So you're just going to turn your back on Chiara?
Maybe we're being too hasty with our decisions, Mom.
Son,
Chiara already made her choice
when she met with Mikoy.
She still hasn't moved on.
She had the opportunity to have Mikoy killed in Italy,
but she couldn't do it.
Which means she still has feelings for Mikoy.
And that will ruin our plans.
-But Mom-- -Son.
I treated her like my own daughter.
I raised her
like she was my own child.
But just like Donatello,
what they did?
They refuse to obey me.
They refuse to listen to me.
It's too late for your Sister Chiara.
Let's think about
what's best for the two of us.
I'm doing this for you.
For you, son.
Because I don't want you to end up like me.
Trampled on and treated like you were nothing by others.
Mom.
I can't do it.
You don't have to.
I know you can't bring yourself to kill Chiara.
What do you mean, Mom?
I already have another option.
One that
will make sure
they won't survive tonight.
Sir.
As far as I know, she's connected to Chiara Valtrovi.
That's how I got information from her.
Chiara Valtrovi is here.
And she's meeting Mikoy Pinagpala.
So why is she giving us this information?
She wants safe passage
for her and her son, Rahmboy.
It looks like the Concordat is betraying Chiara.
Chiara has a shoot-to-kill order.
And if her information is accurate,
then we can take her down.
So, what about Mikoy?
We won't be able to protect Mikoy anymore.
If he's meeting with a known criminal,
that makes him a legitimate target.
We don't have any choice but to take them both down.
I'll prepare the team, sir.
They want something in return.
I'm sorry, Dad.
This is the only way I know.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make whoever did this pay.
This is the life we have.
This is the life that comes with power.
What if I were in that position?
I cannot make a choice.
Real happiness comes with real power.
Being at the top, where no one can bring you down.
When we don't even have the right
to decide our own lives.
We're already at the top.
We have power.
And I intend to keep that.
Isn't there any other choice, Mom?
Is this the only path forward?
This can't happen.
I won't let this happen.
Hello? Who is this?
Brother Mikoy said I should call this number
if I ever needed anything.
What do you need?
This is all about Chiara and Mikoy.
They need our help.
-You know, I can't wait for the weekend. -Bro.
I'll definitely binge watch my favorite series.
For me, it's my K-dramas.
I like that!
Don’t move,
or I'll shoot!
Relax.
I'm not your enemy.
Don't say a word!
What's going on here?
Don't you recognize him?
Lower your guns.
He's Mikoy's secret asset.
What is he doing here?
Exactly.
Weren't you supposed to be in Prague?
I'm here to ask for your help.
Mikoy and Chiara are in danger.
ALEX
This is Mikoy's, right?
Mikoy, where are you?
Oh, Agent Alex, it's Tess.
Mikoy left his phone here.
Is he there?
Oh, do you want me to check outside?
Yes, please. If he's there, please tell him to call me right away.
Okay, sure.
Wait, Agent Alex. Is there a problem?
No, nothing. I just have something I want to ask him.
Thank you.
What?
Did you talk to him?
From what it looks like,
he left behind the device that can help us trace him.
You?
Tell me everything you know
or I'll blow your head off if anything happens to Mikoy.
I can't give you an answer.
This guy's crazy!
But I can take you to someone who knows where they are.
Who?
My very own mother.
Vicky Corales.
The one that hailed as
the Widow's Maid.
But my sense tells me that I should trust you.
Just like the trust Mikoy has in you.
The tracker I planted on you, Chiara, has finally been activated.
Looks like my sweetheart still hasn't changed at all.
If I didn't know you, I'd think you're still that waiter
who works at that cute little café
by the Vltava River.
I loved you
without any conditions.
Then you killed Dad.
Where is Mikoy and Chiara, huh?
Agent Alex, please.
But I don’t have enought time.
At this point, Mikoy and Chiara are probably dead.
I already talked to Agent Dara.
I'll use this to make you feel
what you did to my father.
You idiot, Mikoy.
Don't you dare die.
Wait for me.